Letterpress Copybooks of Samuel Gompers and William Green, Presidents on Microfilm 5431 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 285 - 10/26/1921-11/21/1921 (Reel 285)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 286 - 11/21/1921-12/10/1921 (Reel 286)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 287 - 12/9/1921-1/7/1922, 1921-1922 (Reel 287)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 288 - 1/5/1922-1/24/1922 (Reel 288)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 289 - 1/24/1922-2/22/1922 (Reel 289)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 290 - 2/22/1922-3/15/1922 (Reel 290)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 291 - 3/14/1922-4/4/1922 (Reel 291)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 292 - 4/5/1922-5/8/1922 (Reel 292)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 293 - 5/8/1922-6/27/1922 (Reel 293)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 294 - 6/27/1922-7/31/1922 (Reel 294)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 295 - 7/31/1922-8/30/1922 (Reel 295)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 296 - 8/25/1922-10/3/1922 (Reel 296)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 297 - 10/3/1922-11/3/1922 (Reel 297)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 298 - 11/1/1922-12/6/1922 (Reel 298)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 299 - 12/6/1922-12/29/1922 (Reel 299)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 300 - 12/29/1922-1/25/1923, 1922-1923 (Reel 300)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 301 - 1/25/1923-2/28/1923 (Reel 301)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 302 - 2/27/1923-4/10/1923 (Reel 302)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 303 - 4/11/1923-5/23/1923 (Reel 303)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 304 - 5/1/1923-7/3/1923 (Reel 304)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 305 - 7/3/1923-8/14/1923 (Reel 305)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 306 - 8/14/1923-9/20/1923 (Reel 306)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 307 - 9/20/1923-11/12/1923 (Reel 307)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 308 - 11/10/1923-12/6/1923 (Reel 308)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 309 - 12/7/1923-1/19/1924, 1923-1924 (Reel 309)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 310 - not available (Reel 310)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 311 - 2/25/1924-3/31/1924 (Reel 311)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 312 - 3/31/1924-5/7/1924 (Reel 312)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 313 - not available (Reel 313)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 314 - 6/12/1924-8/25/1924 (Reel 314)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 315 - 8/25/1924-11/20/1924 (Reel 315)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 316 - 11/25/1924-12/15/1924 (Reel 316)
- Samuel Gompers and William Green Letter books vol. 317 - 12/20/1924-1/22/1925, 1924-1925 (Reel 317)
- William Green Letter books vol. 318 - 1/21/1925-2/26/1925 (Reel 318)
- William Green Letter books vol. 319 - 2/25/1925-3/26/1925 (Reel 319)
- William Green Letter books vol. 320 - 3/26/1925-4/23/1925 (Reel 320)
- William Green Letter books vol. 321 - 4/22/1925-5/13/1925 (Reel 321)
- William Green Letter books vol. 322 - 5/13/1925-5/29/1925 (Reel 322)
- William Green Letter books vol. 323 - 5/29/1925-6/4/1925 (Reel 323)
- William Green Letter books vol. 324 - 6/4/1925-6/11/1925 (Reel 324)
- William Green Letter books vol. 325 - 6/10/1925-6/17/1925 (Reel 325)
- William Green Letter books vol. 326 - 6/17/1925-6/25/1925 (Reel 326)
- William Green Letter books vol. 327 - 6/25/1925-6/30/1925 (Reel 327)
- William Green Letter books vol. 328 - 7/1/1925-7/14/1925 (Reel 328)
- William Green Letter books vol. 329 - 7/11/1925-7/16/1925 (Reel 329)
- William Green Letter books vol. 330 - 7/17/1925-7/24/1925 (Reel 330)
- William Green Letter books vol. 331 - 7/24/1925-8/4/1925 (Reel 331)
- S. William Green Letter books vol. 332 - 8/3/1925-8/5/1925 (Reel 332)
- William Green Letter books vol. 333 - 8/5/1925-8/12/1925 (Reel 333)
- William Green Letter books vol. 334 - 8/15/1925-8/20/1925 (Reel 334)
- William Green Letter books vol. 335 - 8/12/1925-8/26/1925 (Reel 334)
- William Green Letter books vol. 335 - 8/12/1925-8/26/1925 (Reel 335)
- William Green Letter books vol. 326 - 8/26/1925-8/29/1925 (Reel 336)
- William Green Letter books vol. 337 - 8/29/1925-9/3/1925 (Reel 337)
- William Green Letter books vol. 338 - 9/3/1925-9/10/1925 (Reel 338)
- William Green Letter books vol. 339 - 9/10/1925-9/16/1925 (Reel 339)
- William Green Letter books vol. 340 - 9/16/1925-9/21/1925 (Reel 340)
- William Green Letter books vol. 341 - 9/22/1925-9/28/1925 (Reel 341)
- William Green Letter books vol. 342 - 9/29/1925-10/5/1925 (Reel 342)
- William Green Letter books vol. 343 - 9/28/1925-10/22/1925 (Reel 343)
- William Green Letter books vol. 344 - 10/22/1925-10/23/1925 (Reel 344)
- William Green Letter books vol. 345 - 10/23/1925-10/30/1925 (Reel 345)
- William Green Letter books vol. 346 - 10/29/1925-10/30/1925 (Reel 346)
- William Green Letter books vol. 347 - 10/30/1925-11/5/1925 (Reel 347)
- William Green Letter books vol. 348 - 11/5/1925-11/6/1925 (Reel 348)
- William Green Letter books vol. 349 - 11/4/1925-11/10/1925 (Reel 349)
- William Green Letter books vol. 350 - 11/10/1925-11/16/1925 (Reel 350)
- William Green Letter books vol. 351 - 11/16/1925-11/17/1925 (Reel 351)
- William Green Letter books vol. 352 - 11/19/1925-11/23/1925 (Reel 352)
- William Green Letter books vol. 353 - 11/23/1925-11/25/1925 (Reel 353)
- William Green Letter books vol. 354 - 11/25/1925-12/1/1925 (Reel 354)
- William Green Letter books vol. 355 - 11/16/1925-11/17/1925 (Reel 355)